# SID DADLANI

Phone: +852 3051 9194 / +91 99874 01155

Email: sid.dadlani@gmail.com / sid.dadlani@me.com

Focus of Interest: Asset Management/ Private Equity/ Business Development/ Institutional Sales

DIRECTOR / PARTNER / STRATEGY HEAD – seeking a leadership position which combines an All American education, work experience and corporate skills with a competitive drive and in depth knowledge of EMEA investment market culture and very deep Asian roots.

#### **Qualifications Profile**

Accomplished -- highly results-driven, with extensive years of progressive experience and extraordinary success. Exhibited career-long track record of proactive leadership in developing strategic visions and delivering results. A creative strategizer with the ability to communicate effectively across management levels, geographies & disciplines.

Personally known to Banks, Sovereign, Corporations, Pensions in Middle East and Across Asia.

#### **Professional Skills**

**Fund Raises and Placements** 

- Successfully helped in Raising 6 Alternative Asset funds in the last eight years
- Fixed Income in Real Estate, Life Sciences, 2 in Infrastructure and 2 in Real Estate
- A contributor in generating a weighted average IRR of 74% and multiple of invested capital of 4.8 by performing as a member of the Investment Committee that approved investments

Strategy, Vision and Mission Planning

- Served as an operating member of deal teams in providing operating perspective and assessment of management, business plans, management process & value
- Initiated a formalized strategic planning process to establish core values and brand promise while assuming responsibility in managing post-acquisition value-add which included strategic planning & assessment
- Assisted advisors and shareholders in restructuring and redefining business strategy and model

Collaborative Leadership and Growth

- Assisted advisors and shareholders in restructuring and redefining business strategy/model
- Formed and supervised 2 separate teams in 2 separate organizations that represented more than 43 aggregate years of private equity investing experience
- Executed cross-functional management process and culture that decreased cost, improved capacity and provided business continuity

### **Work Experience**

### **RELIGARE GLOBAL ASSET MANAGEMENT**

Hong Kong / Dubai (Oct. 2014 – Present)

Global Head of Distribution, CEO (mena)

Set up a team that has complete responsibility for raising a total of over a U\$1bn over a period of 3 years for 4 affiliates that are sponsored internal funds; **3 finished and 1 ongoing.**Religare Global Asset Management (RGAM) is a multi-boutique asset management platform focused on alternatives. The RGAM operating philosophy is to partner with best breed of asset managers (Affiliates) in various alternative asset classes. RGAM also builds out organic ventures with distinctive capabilities. With a presence across the US and Asia; an aggregate AUM of USD \$20bn (31<sup>st</sup> December 2015), RGAM has emerged as a significant asset management platform.

- Placed (RCOF) Religare Credit Advisors a 3 year close ended direct lending fixed income fund raised to U\$90million in the third quarter of 2015.
- Helped complete second round Quadria Capital in the second quarter of 2015 (a U\$330million growth capital fund investing in South Asia in life sciences).
- Helped raise U\$150million for Northgate Capita (an affiliated owned by RGAM) first Venture Capital Fund of Funds in record 3 months in primarily China.

# SID DADLANI

Phone: +852 3051 9194 / +91 99874 01155

Email: sid.dadlani@gmail.com / sid.dadlani@me.com

IL&FS ADVISORSDubai / Hong KongChief Marketing Officer & Head of Business Development(Jan. 2010 – Sept, 2014)

Headed a team responsible for raising a total of **U\$600mn over a period of 4years** for 3 fully deployed Group funds. IL&FS Investment Managers Limited (IIML) is one of the oldest and largest private equity fund managers in South Asia, with over U\$3.2bn under management. Investors to IIML-managed Funds include most of the major Indian Banks & Institutions, and marquee Global Institutional Investors including major U.S. Pension Funds, Endowments and Foundations. IIML is listed on the National Stock Exchange & Bombay Exchange.

- Placed Souq (IISF) a U\$290mn fund investing in the MENA region in Infrastructure projects in a mezzanine structure in the fourth quarter of 2014.
- Raised DCL U\$110million through April'12. The fund was fully deployed successfully in 1year. Dia Capital returned an IRR of 32% in its first year
- Undeviating Responsibility for Corporate Affairs & Strategic Planning, Investment & Committee Recommendations, Management of Investor Relations and Investments.

#### **KOTAK MAHINDRA CAPITAL**

Mumbai

Vice President – Head of Global Markets

(Dec. 2007 - Dec. 2009)

Joined Kotak to enhance its global reach and promote its cross border business. Created and Headed the Global Markets Team with an approach that gave it the competitive edge to generate value-added tools and structure state-of-the-art deals through M&A, PE and Capital Market Transactions. Provided a full range of financial advisory services for mergers, acquisitions, joint ventures, and leveraged buyouts; Lead Originator for 2008.

- Advised Mahindra & Mahindra in buying a 67.9% stake in JECO Holding AG of Germany. This acquisition worth Euro140mn was the largest outbound auto parts acquisition in the world at the time.
- Raised MPC-Syn in 2008&2009 a U\$270mn, retail real estate fund from a record single investor for IL&FS Investment Managers Limited (IIML). MPSy an in-house portfolio fund investing into 3 retail Real Estate Companies for their 17 projects Panning India
- Played a key pricing, marketing and placement role in the successful IPO of South India's largest Real Estate Co. in 2007

JP MORGAN CHASE

Associate Vice President - Real Estate & Energy

ROBERT FLEMING Co. (Acquired and merged with JP Morgan Chase 1999)

Intern, Analyst

New York

(May 1997 – Dec. 1998)

Senior Member and Team Leader on the Global M&A Transaction side. Responsible for client development and deal transaction on buy side advisory assignments, sale mandates, spin offs or split offs; engaged an executive team of 6 for performing various functions across the board. The origination team was the leader for the firm in 2004 and 2005 for Non Japan Asia and Europe. Collaborated to develop and execute transactions tailored to the marketplace and for each client.

## The methodology generated deals consistently to outperform in the aftermarket.

- Advised and played an essential origination role on the US\$2.55bn Reliance Energy (Texas), the world's largest privately financed pipeline in operation
- Advised GE Capital Real Estate on the divestiture of Security Capital Research &
   Management Inc("SCR&M"),(an institutional Real Estate Manager) to Bank One Corp
- Advised the Rockefeller Group in its acquisition of CommonWealth Partners LLC, a private equity real estate investment manager

# SID DADLANI

Phone: +852 3051 9194 / +91 99874 01155

Email: sid.dadlani@gmail.com / sid.dadlani@me.com

**Education** 

**NEW YORK UNIVERSITY** New York, New York (1997)

Bachelor of Arts in International Business

STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK Stony Brook, New York (1999)

Masters in Finance of Business Administration

Internship

**COMMERCE BANK** (summer training program) New York (May 1995 – Aug. 1995)

Working of Foreign Exchange Treasury and the Scope of Middle Markets

### **Additional Information**

- o +8 Handicap Golfer
- o Actively donate time & efforts on various philanthropic endeavors in their own right